[SPEAKER_01]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's play another game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This time you are guessing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am thinking about an animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please start asking me questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it able to swim?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not known for swimming.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd throw you a life jacket, but we're on dry land with this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a carnivore?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is a carnivore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chomp chomp.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got some sharp teeth on that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it have scales?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it does not have scales.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like you're fishing for clues in the wrong pond.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a canine?
[SPEAKER_01]: In a jiffy?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it is not a canine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe try howling up a different tree.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it part of the... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it part of the cat family?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is part of the cat family.
[SPEAKER_01]: Perfect, you're clawing your way to the top.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it known to reside in a jungle?
[SPEAKER_01]: Reflecting on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not typically associated with the jungle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like the king of the jungle moniker doesn't apply here.
[SPEAKER_01]: In a jiffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it doesn't reside in the jungle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like you're not quite the king of this particular guessing jungle yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it live in the savannah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Excuse me, I need to think a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it does reside in the savannah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hot, hot, hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your instincts are on a safari to success.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it have a mane?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it does have a mane.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looking sharp.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're nearly the king of this guessing game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a lion?
[SPEAKER_01]: You have asked 10 questions and have to guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is a lion.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guessed correctly.