[SPEAKER_01]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's play another game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This time you are guessing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am thinking about an animal.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the animal larger than a human?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is larger than a human.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not sizing me up to quickly, are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Does the animal live on land?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it does reside on land.
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely towering over the competition with that guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a second.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a domesticated animal?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it does reside on land.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not beating around the bush, are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it domesticated?
[SPEAKER_00]: A domestic animal?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it is not a domestic animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like someone's barking up the wrong family tree.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a carnivore?
[SPEAKER_00]: Quick scan.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not a carnivore.
[SPEAKER_01]: You might want to sharpen those claws of thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to say something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a lot heavier than a human?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is significantly heavier than a human.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're definitely not lightweight in your questioning.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it an elephant?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, your guess is not correct.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep trunkting along with those questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Quick scan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the animal dangerous to humans?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not considered dangerous to humans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry, you won't need any armor for this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does the animal have any patterns on itself?
[SPEAKER_01]: Reflecting on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have asked 10 questions and have to guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the animal, a giraffe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am sorry you guessed wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: This concludes this round of the game.