[SPEAKER_00]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's play another game.
[SPEAKER_00]: This time you are guessing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am thinking about an animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does the animal usually swim in water?
[SPEAKER_00]: Please start asking me questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does the animal live in water?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it does not reside in water.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hope you're not fishing for clues in the wrong pond.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does your animal fly?
[SPEAKER_00]: Swiftly checking.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it does not fly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seems like your guesses are having a bit of turbulence.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does your animal usually reside in Europe?
[SPEAKER_00]: Excuse me, I need to think a bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it can reside in Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eureka.
[SPEAKER_00]: somewhat closer to the truth you are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is your animal usually kept as a pet?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it is usually kept as a pet.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're barking up the right weight.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not supposed to say that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Keep fetching those questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is your animal carnivorous?
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to say something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it is carnivorous.
[SPEAKER_00]: Salivating at the rate scent I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does your animal... Is your... Swiftly checking.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think you might have missed a part of your question there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was certainly a mysterious attempt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is your animal a type of cat?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it is not a type of cat.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're barking up the wrong tree with that guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Try a different category, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is your animal a type of dog?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it is a dog you guessed correctly.
[SPEAKER_00]: This concludes this round of the game.