[SPEAKER_01]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's play another game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This time you are guessing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am thinking about an animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does it have four legs?
[SPEAKER_01]: Please start asking me questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it have four legs?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it does not have four legs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep on your toes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You might just stumble on the answer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Does it have more than four legs?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it does not have four legs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like you took a tiny misstep there, don't trip over your own questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to say something?
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it have more than four legs?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it does not have more than four legs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely not crawling with possibilities, are we?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a reptile?
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to say something.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just a second.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it is not a reptile.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it live in the water?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not slithering towards the answer this time.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to say something?
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it live in the water?
[SPEAKER_01]: Engaging deeper thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it resides in the water.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not floundering anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep swimming for the answer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a type of fish?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you're asking if it's a fish.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cast a wider net, but you're swimming in the right school now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it larger than a cat?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is larger than a cat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seems like you're not fishing for compliments, just bigger fish.
[SPEAKER_00]: Would you consider this animal dangerous?
[SPEAKER_01]: In a jiffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is considered dangerous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Careful now, don't bite off more than you can chew with your guesses.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it extra dangerous for surfers?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is particularly risky for those who surf.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're definitely riding the wave to success now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does it have very many teeth?
[SPEAKER_01]: in a jiffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have asked him questions and have to guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a shark?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is a shark.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guessed correctly.
[SPEAKER_01]: This concludes this round of the game.