[SPEAKER_00]: Hi there, let's play 10 questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the animal you're thinking of typically kept as a pet?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: That certainly narrows it down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the animal you're thinking of small enough to be held in your arms?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: A wonderful that narrows it down quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is this animal a type of rodent?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not quite sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, then back to the drawing board it seems.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does this animal have fur?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, splendid.
[SPEAKER_00]: That narrows it down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does this animal have fur?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_00]: Ah, that's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seems like I'm getting closer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it known for its ability to purr?
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you repeat that again?
[SPEAKER_00]: To purr?
[SPEAKER_00]: What does that mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm gonna skip this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the animal primarily a carnivore known for eating meat?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, no?
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, I need to consider other options.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, yes, but not raw meat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it a type of bird?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if I thought I was out to do something interesting, let's see, what else could it be?
[SPEAKER_00]: Does this animal commonly reside indoors?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, both, but more or less indoors, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I'm getting warmer with this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is this animal prone to climbing or jumping onto elevated surfaces like furniture?
[SPEAKER_01]: It depends on what species.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some yes, some no.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have asked my questions and have failed to guess correctly.
[SPEAKER_00]: This concludes this round of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll try again next time.